We've reached the end of the dialogue.
我们已经到了对话的结尾。
Hopefully you've learned a lot about how different things are described in hotels.
希望您已经了解了很多关于酒店中如何描述不同事物的知识。
And if you need to how to actually make a booking.
如果您需要如何实际进行预订。
Now at the end it's the job of the receptionist to confirm to confirm the booking all the details just
现在最后是接待员的工作来确认确认预订的所有细节
to make sure it's all right.
以确保一切正常。
OK now we did a confirmation before when we were talking about inviting a friend to do something.
好的，现在我们在谈论邀请朋友做某事之前进行了确认。
The person who calls needs to confirm.
打电话的人需要确认。
Well in this case it's the business that needs to confirm because they're the ones who are going to
好吧，在这种情况下，需要确认的是业务，因为他们将要确认
provide the service.
提供服务。
They're the ones who are going to take your money.
他们是要拿走你钱的人。
Right.
正确的。
So they should confirm but we confirm in the same way we always confirm with the words so and it's so
所以他们应该确认，但我们以同样的方式确认，我们总是用 so 和 it's so 来确认
easy to confirm things.
容易确认的事情。
So then you just say the basic details you're all set.
因此，您只需说出基本的细节就可以了。
All set means nothing more needs to be done nothing more needs to be done.
一切就绪意味着不再需要做任何事情。
You're all set with five nights in the deluxe could say deluxe room from the 18th checking out on the
从 18 号退房开始，您就已经准备好在豪华房住五晚了
twenty third.
第二十三。
Thank you so much.
太感谢了。
OK.
好的。
Now if somebody says all set they might be answering the question.
现在，如果有人说一切就绪，他们可能正在回答这个问题。
Do I need to do anything else.
我还需要做什么吗。
If you buy something if you want to maybe refund something or whatever you can ask them.
如果你买了一些东西，如果你想退还一些东西，或者你可以问他们什么。
A customer service person.
一个客服人员。
What else do I need to do.
我还需要做什么。
Do you need my card.
你需要我的卡吗？
What.
什么。
No you're all set.
不，你都准备好了。
You're all set.
你都准备好了。
Means nothing else needs to happen.
意味着没有其他事情需要发生。
Go go go.
去！去！去。
You're finished.
你完了。
Have a nice day.
祝你今天过得愉快。
Very very common.
非常非常常见。
OK.
好的。
We look forward to seeing you on the 18th.
我们期待在 18 日与您相见。
And thanks for booking with us.
感谢您与我们预订。
Have a great day.
祝你有美好的一天。
Now why use us.
现在为什么要使用我们。
Why use we.
为什么要使用我们。
Well because this is just one person representing the organization the hotel and so if they say I look
好吧，因为这只是代表酒店组织的一个人，所以如果他们说我看起来
forward to seeing you it feels like you're the only person who works here.
期待见到你，感觉就像你是唯一在这里工作的人。
You're gonna be here when I come.
我来的时候你会在这里。
How do I know that.
我怎么知道。
How do you know that.
你怎么知道。
Right.
正确的。
So it's actually very professional to use.
所以使用起来其实很专业。
We look forward to and us when it's a situation where there's not a personal relationship between the
我们期待和我们之间没有私人关系的情况
person who called and the receptionist.
打电话的人和接待员。
It's a relationship between the business and the person who called.
这是企业和打电话的人之间的关系。
So if it's that sort of relationship we means anybody who's working here when you check in it's going
所以如果是那种关系，我们是指任何在你登记入住时在这里工作的人
to be the person who sees you on the 18th.
成为18日见到你的人。
Right.
正确的。
So that's why we use we.
所以这就是我们使用我们的原因。
That's why we use us when you're talking about your company that you represent and you're just one person
这就是为什么当您谈论您所代表的公司并且您只是一个人时，我们使用我们
and maybe you're going to have a day off when this person actually comes to the hotel and maybe also
也许当这个人真的来酒店时你会休息一天，也许还有
when they check out or maybe today's your last day of work and you're never coming back here again.
当他们退房时，或者今天是你工作的最后一天，你再也不会回到这里了。
Well that's why it's best to use we look forward to seeing you.
这就是为什么最好使用我们期待见到您的原因。
Thank you for booking Have a nice day.
感谢您的预订祝您有美好的一天。
All right.
好的。
Thank you so much as a very polite way to say thank you.
非常感谢您，这是一种非常礼貌的表示感谢的方式。
That's a little bit formal but it's very common for service related situations.
这有点正式，但在与服务相关的情况下很常见。
So that's it for our dialogue.
这就是我们的对话。
We are going to go on though and I'm going to show you just a couple other ways we can say goodbye.
我们会继续，我会向您展示我们可以说再见的其他几种方式。
Just so you know OK.
就这样你知道了。
But I hope that you feel comfortable now to call the hotel and make a booking and I would encourage
但我希望您现在可以放心地打电话给酒店并进行预订，我会鼓励您
you next time you want to book a hotel instead of doing it on a Web site or an app try to call challenge
下次您想预订酒店而不是在网站或应用程序上预订时，请尝试致电挑战
yourself.
你自己。